(function() {
  window.fossils_key = [
    {
      key_pair: 1,
      question: "The fossil resembles a modern day seashell",
      next_question_pair: 2
    }, {
      key_pair: 1,
      question: "The fossil does not resembles a modern day seashell",
      next_question_pair: 8
    }, {
      key_pair: 2,
      question: "The top side of the fossil is rounded with ribs",
      next_question_pair: 3
    }, {
      key_pair: 2,
      question: "The top and bottom of the fossil hae ribs and ridges",
      next_question_pair: 5
    }, {
      key_pair: 3,
      question: "The fossil has a circle or oval outline shape",
      next_question_pair: 4
    }, {
      key_pair: 3,
      question: "The fossil has a flat semi-circle shape",
      answer: "Dunbarella PELECYPOD"
    }, {
      key_pair: 4,
      question: "The fossil has a circular outline with light ribs",
      answer: "Glycimeris PELECYPOD"
    }, {
      key_pair: 4,
      question: "The fossil has an oval outline with a very pointed pedicle",
      answer: "Lima PELECYPOD"
    }, {
      key_pair: 5,
      question: "The fossil is larger than pinky fingernail",
      next_question_pair: 6
    }, {
      key_pair: 5,
      question: "The fossil is approximate pinky fingernail size",
      answer: "Zygospira BRACHIOPOD"
    }, {
      key_pair: 6,
      question: "The fossil has very distinct ribs",
      next_question_pair: 7
    }, {
      key_pair: 6,
      question: "The fossil has faint ribs with a predominant central ridge",
      answer: "Schuchertella BRACHIOPOD"
    }, {
      key_pair: 7,
      question: "The fossil has large ribs and very slight ridge",
      answer: "Platystrophia BRACHIOPOD"
    }, {
      key_pair: 7,
      question: "The fossil has predominant ridge and valley",
      answer: "Spirifer BRACHIOPOD"
    }, {
      key_pair: 8,
      question: "The fossil is long and tubular (tube shape) or conical (cone shape)",
      next_question_pair: 9
    }, {
      key_pair: 8,
      question: "The fossil is ribbed with three sections and a lip",
      answer: "Flexicalymene TRILOBYTE"
    }, {
      key_pair: 9,
      question: "The fossil is tubular",
      next_question_pair: 10
    }, {
      key_pair: 9,
      question: "The fossil is conical",
      next_question_pair: 12
    }, {
      key_pair: 10,
      question: "The fossil has round sections",
      next_question_pair: 11
    }, {
      key_pair: 10,
      question: "The fossil is branching with pin holes",
      answer: "Rhombopora BRYOZOAN"
    }, {
      key_pair: 11,
      question: "The fossil is thin like a pencil and has holes on cross-section",
      answer: "Taxocrinus CRINOID"
    }, {
      key_pair: 11,
      question: "The fossil is wide with elongating ribs",
      answer: "Dolorthosceras CEPHALOPOD"
    }, {
      key_pair: 12,
      question: "The fossil has a spiral shape",
      answer: "GASTROPOD"
    }, {
      key_pair: 12,
      question: "The fossil resembles a dinosaur tooth with radial sections",
      answer: "Streptelasma HORN CORAL"
    }
  ];
}).call(this);
